<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hashmap.dev</title>
    <link>https://hashmap.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on hashmap.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 17:29:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hashmap.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks and papers</title>
      <link>https://hashmap.dev/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 17:29:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hashmap.dev/talks/</guid>
      <description> Upcoming  Grin intro, Buidl Asia, Seoul, July 22-23 Grin development: as little as possible, Web3 Summit, Berlin, August 19-21  Past  How to start contributing to Grin, grincon0, Berlin, November 2018 slides video A Conversation on Privacy, a panel discussion with Daniel J. Bernstein, Vlad Zamfir and all, 35C3, Leipzig, December 2018 page, video wanted Building Mimblewimble/Grin, an implementation for privacy and scalability, Quentin Le Sceller (Grin Dev Team), Ignotus Peverell (Grin Dev Team), Yeastplume (Grin Dev Team), Antioch Peverell (Grin Dev Team), hashmap (Grin Dev Team), John Tromp (Grin Dev Team), Daniel Lehnberg (Grin Dev Team), Speaker: Quentin Le Sceller, Stanford, January 2019 page video Grin mainnet launch and first weeks, Grin Berlin meetup, February 2019 Как работает Mimblewibmle, Moscow, May 2019, in Russian slides  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://hashmap.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 17:17:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hashmap.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a grin core developer, a member of Grin council and a co-founder of cycle42. Also I work on a Grin payment processor Knockturn Allee.
I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD in CS, I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing software for 20+ years, contributing to OpenStack, Cloud Foundry, and started Klar. Contact me if you need some consulting for your Grin (or Rust) project alexey@cycle42.com
Last but not least I&amp;rsquo;m a marathon runner (3:19, M40).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>